{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567076871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567076870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f1350119-7be9-4677-8e63-f4df2b04d5ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567088843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567088843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567092574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567092574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567094115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567094115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567097878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567097878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567099441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567099440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567103277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567103277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567104847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567104847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567107872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567107872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567109434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567109434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567113612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567113611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567115182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567115182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567118549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567118549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567120193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567120193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567123582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567123582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567125138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567125137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567128452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567128451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567130015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567130015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567133555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567133555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567135129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567135129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567139649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567139649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567141660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567141660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567141927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567141927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567147525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567147525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" f256fa56-e7f4-4f27-aac2-6f922b2ec659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567156221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567156221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_k-h-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567159408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567159408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567162664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567162664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_i-e-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567166297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567166297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_r-z-ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567170796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567170796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-m-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567175011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567175011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567178774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567178774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567193188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567193187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-n-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567206067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567206067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_e-ch-o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567217329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567217329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_w-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567223072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567223069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083109"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_w-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}